Hey, what colors do you think Hori-senpai would like best?
I've seen her wear red and pink accessories before,
so maybe warmer colors?
Bound to beat something blue or white, yeah?
Are you even listening?
Hello? You in there?
Go home.
If anyone knows the answer, it's you.
Please go home.
Why won't you just tell me what her favorite colors are?
Sawada, I am begging you.
You realize Valentine's Day is right around the corner
and I can't wrap her present until I know which color we're going to use!
Don't ask her boyfriend about it, jeez!
It's important for a gift's wrapping to be as cute and appealing as possible.
Don't you get it?
I know it looks nice, though it's not like I've dwelled on it.
The art of gift wrap, huh?
Hold on a friggin' minute here.
Are you planning to let the shop wrap your present?
Well, what you choose doesn't involve me.
But it's cute and appealing when they wrap it.
Though I'm willing to learn your way as well.
Holly!
I wish I knew which one to pick!
Red and orange are the colors I found Horimo's partial to.
See?
That wasn't so hard now, right?
Ooh!
Check out this simple yet sweet wrapping here!
キット知らないだろう
捨ててしまいたい過去
二人の助手だと
意味をくれたこと
キット知らないだろう
キミが呼ぶ僕の名前
キット知らないより大きな意味をくれたこと
飲み干した甘いサイダー
見せ返る僕を笑った
作った笑顔なんかも
減らないね
どうしてどうして
どうして
もらって
中にいる僕を
愛しいというの
僕は何も
返して
生きて
生きるんだろうが
眩しい思いが
満ちていく
この感情の
名前をそっと
キミに伝えよ
幸せ
キャンヤン
バガー
新た兄が
He'll be disappointed to get diddly-squat.
Diddly is far better than my lousy sweets, I guarantee it.
Well, in Remy's opinion,
he'd be happy to receive any gift from you.
She's underestimating how yucky that gift could be.
10-4.
What's up, you two?
Oh, you know, just shoot in the breeze!
You over here for class, or...?
I had a little business to handle with me, I wanna...
It's almost time, and I'm as ready as ever!
This year, I'll pull out all the stops.
What stops?
Miyamura and I had a long talk about what kind of...
Come on, Sawada!
Don't wanna be late for class, right?
Let's go!
I'll look like a total loser
if she finds out I'm stressing over the gift grab!
Any idea what that was about?
None.
Jeez!
Would it kill him to empathize with me just a little?
That memory's gonna take me off for weeks!
Um, can we talk?
I guess.
Aren't you, um, really good friends with some third-year students here?
This again?
I'd say so.
But why are you asking?
Well, Valentine's Day is coming up.
Mm-hmm.
And there's this guy.
I'm almost positive he's one you hang out with.
Which one, though?
Oh, um, thing is...
Is it Yanagi or Miyamura?
Regardless, I can pass on your gift.
Um, I don't know either of those boys.
Are these seniors?
Huh?
Is it Ishikawa?
Maybe Sengoku?
No, those names aren't ringing bells either.
They aren't?
Sorry, but he must be a third-year that I don't know.
I think you do.
He's the only person in your group who always wears a hoodie to school.
Okay, Yura's your guy.
Wait, that's who you met?!
Oh, from the way you said that, I take it you have a thing for him?
I'm sorry.
There is zero romance between us, but, well, this mystery man is Yura?
Mm-hmm.
Is this a prank?
It's not.
He's so outgoing and energetic and...
Oh gosh, I feel myself flushing.
He doesn't even know I exist since we haven't spoken a word to each other, but...
Everybody loves getting a Valentine's treat and this is my last chance since he's about to graduate!
Wait!
Jeez, calm down, I get it.
Deep breaths.
I'm worried he won't accept it if he has a girlfriend.
He doesn't, so don't.
You sound pretty sure.
What if they're keeping you low-key?
There's no way.
You should make a move.
Ask him out.
No!
I just want to give him some chocolate.
That's all it is.
Dating him isn't my goal.
Hmm.
This is great.
I've wanted to talk to someone about this for a while.
None of our classmates would know who he is, though.
Didn't think I'd get so flustered from saying it out loud.
I'll listen if you need me to.
You know, since I can't really help you out beyond that.
If it's okay, could you ask him what kind of chocolate he likes for me, please?
You really want to give some sugar without getting any back?
So you admire him from afar?
Yes.
That sounds about right.
It's that time of year.
Store shelves are going to be packed with Valentine's stuff everywhere.
I feel you, man.
But you're one of those guys who's going to be swimming in chocolate treats,
so maybe I don't feel you.
You already said you did.
No takebacks.
So, any plans for the lovey-dovey day?
Uh, practice tying a tie?
Yeah.
Is that what Miyamura's teaching you now?
He said he wants to practice, too.
Ta-da!
No, it's not appealing at all.
Yeah, you think?
I thought I tied it the way Sawada's magazine said to.
What is this monstrosity?
It's freaking tight, dude!
I cannot tie your stupid knot!
Huh?
Hey, Sawada just showed up, guys.
I'm guessing you came from Miyamura.
No.
Oh, hey, Sawada.
I'm actually here for you, Iura.
Me?
Really?
What's up, Dudette?
Um, do you like chocolate or no?
Oh!
G-could it be?
I mean, it's gotta be.
Valentine's Day research!
Yes, I like chocolate.
Do you have a favorite?
I love them all.
I'll be bitter or sweet, and I have no known allergies.
Gay.
Hmm.
Might as well sky-write how desperate you are, Shu.
So, yeah, any kind of chocolate works.
Got it.
Thanks, Iura.
And he cut it off!
Huh?
You want to spend time and cash on chocolate for Shu?
Wait.
Shock someone besides Toadie is on your list.
Shut your mouths right now before you discourage her, you killjoys!
Hey, if you want to make me sweets, that's your prerogative, okay?
Ugh.
What kind of warped illusion did you invent to think I'd make sweets for you?
Huh?
I'm going back to class.
Where things make sense.
Huh?
What?
She's the one who's not making sense, you know?
Pilata is playing love games, my dude.
I knew that wasn't what she was after.
Chocolate!
He said it doesn't matter what kind you get him.
Works for me.
That just means I have a lot of options and time to choose.
It'd be easier if you narrowed it down.
There are just so many.
Thanks for coming to help me pick out something.
Don't sweat it.
I'm giving chocolates to someone special, too, so I wanted to see what they have.
So you've also got someone special?
Oh, well, yes, but it's a secret.
Aww.
If I can't give this to him, will you accept it instead?
Don't worry, you'll do it.
I know you will.
I'll try my best.
It's nearly here.
Well, in Remy's humble opinion, he'd be happy to receive any gift from you.
Okay.
Um, what's a chocolate dessert that's so easy to make, not even a novice could botch it?
Hmm.
Oh, so you decided to make something for Miyamoto, then?
Huh?
The walls have ears and I don't want that chair!
We're the only ones in here and everyone knows you're dating.
Miyamoto bakes, so I don't want him to find out I asked you instead.
It won't be as pretty as the store-bought stuff, and I'm sure it's gonna be an acquired taste at best.
But if there's anything I can't screw up entirely, am I really gonna give the simplest dessert on the planet to a cake shop owner's son?
As simple as possible, but still delicious.
Hmm.
I'll be right back.
Whoa, too cool!
Our school has recipe books?
It does.
And the ones in here are very easy to follow.
I would check this book out on the regular when I started learning how to make desserts.
Oh, chocolate desserts.
Ah, here it is.
This one would be perfect for you.
Kono's desserts are fantastic.
But even she had to start somewhere.
Here I go!
Can I please eat this candy bar? I'm starving!
Out, Kyousuke!
Let's try not to bother Kyoko when she's wielding weaponry, okay, honey?
She's not preparing for war.
Is she?
What are you about to cook?
Can we watch?
I kinda need space, so you gotta watch from over there.
Is it for anything special?
Well, yeah, I guess so.
It's, uh, Valentine's Day practice.
It should be for Halloween since her face is so scary.
Is she gonna fight her boyfriend?
Hey!
Get out of here and let me concentrate!
It's yours when it's done!
Scary!
Ah!
Of course I have a scary look.
This is serious!
He may be happy no matter what,
but he'll be happier if it tastes decent.
It's not really good.
Ugh!
Um...
Oh!
Um, I see!
Way to go, dummy!
Huh?
Uh, I'm here!
I'm gonna eat one!
Yuna!
No, don't!
Yeah, I'll try one, too!
I'll go ahead and take one as well.
Please spare yourself!
The stomach aches, everyone!
It's not bad.
I couldn't eat a bunch at once,
but it's all right.
It's edible, then?
Kids like soda would never go for this.
He might like bittersweet stuff when he's grown.
I think they're perfect, though.
So, more for me.
Hey, that was the biggest piece on the plate, Yuri!
So, it's good?
Depends on your taste!
Just tell me whether it's good or not!
I don't know if it's good or not!
Hori, please don't be so discouraged.
I either like talent or taste or both.
Self-deprecating thoughts like that won't help,
so drop it now!
Oh...
In all honesty,
I think you're worrying over nothing, Hori.
Yes, it's bitter,
but a lot of guys prefer not-so-sweet sweets.
Look, I can handle the truth!
I promise I won't rage if you tell it to me straight!
You're already getting hysterical, though!
They're awful.
From the taste to the lumpy shape.
Hey, remember what Remy said?
Huh?
Miyamura will be over the moon
to receive any present you make for him, right?
Store-bought stuff might look prettier
and have a taste a lot of people love,
but that's not what matters with most gifts.
Besides,
I really like yours!
Know why?
It reminds me of you.
Oh, no!
I was, um,
not expecting a back hug!
She's right.
What matters most when it comes to gifts is...
Happy Valentine's Day!
You're gonna make me blush.
I feel special.
What?
They aren't romantic sweets.
I figured that.
No harm done.
Hey!
Yuda!
Your obligatory chocolate, sir.
Can't you at least call it friendship chocolate?
Ooh!
The Miyamura cake shop brand.
The Ayori cake shop brand.
There isn't a girl in school
who brought more chocolate than him.
This is true.
How do you wait?
Can you come over today?
I'll work it in.
Would right after school be good?
Yeah, okay.
Then again,
I need a little time before you get there,
so just walk slow.
In that case,
I'll stop by my place first.
If you feel like it's too dark before you head out,
Colin, I'll come get you.
I'll be fine.
Then I'll see you later.
Must have to prep his gift.
I thought it'd just be homemade sweets,
but he didn't bring it to school
and apparently can't bring it to my house.
How big is this thing?
What is it?
I'm dying to know!
Bodhi-senpai!
Happy Valentine's Day!
I made this gift just for you!
It's full of my hard work and love!
Thank you, but you shouldn't have.
This is what she pulled out all the stops for.
Aww!
It's so cute!
I'm glad you like it!
Really glad!
This darling little bow is a great color.
I'm almost sad to untie it.
Miyamura knows you best.
He said you like orange.
I can't even begin to describe how annoying it was to get help from him,
but he was positive that one would make you smile.
He knew it'd make me smile.
I love it!
Thank you!
Maybe seeing someone you like with a big, goofy grin on their face
is what today is really all about.
Good!
Both of you are here!
Special delivery!
What is it?
We'll call it a choco-gram.
I'm giving them to everyone so they're kind of tiny,
but they're a lot better than last year's batch.
Oh, wow!
I'll save it for when I get home, okay?
Yes, so will I!
Don't wait too long!
Bye!
It's like a storm blew through here.
Yoshikawa!
You called?
I also have a special delivery thing.
Here.
Oh, I'll make sure it gets to him.
I appreciate it, but, um,
look inside first, okay?
What?
See ya.
She wants me to see his gift?
Guess she got him too.
Huh?
I'm not too early, am I?
Hope not.
Believe it or not, you're right on time.
Have a seat.
Where's your mom?
She should be home soon.
Uh-huh.
I wonder if he'll like his chocolate.
He's nice to a fault,
so he'll probably say it's awesome
even if he wants to gag.
Thanks for waiting.
Mi amor-
Happy Valentine's Day.
I thought I'd go with a classic Valentine cake.
It smells so good!
You don't mind if I go ahead and dig in, do you?
Thanks!
Oh.
Delicious as always.
I was kind of holding my breath for a hot minute there.
You were honestly worried I wouldn't like your cake?
Well, uh, the cake itself wasn't what worried me.
The gift wrap, though.
As you see, I struggled to figure that out.
If it hadn't looked nice enough,
I would have brought it to your house.
Hmm?
Sorry it's not fancier, despite this being a special day.
I didn't even think to gift wrap my stinking homemade chocolate.
Fancy-schmancy!
This is great!
I love it!
What a relief.
Well, I can't fix it now.
I also made you something,
since we're Valentine's and all.
Oh.
I wondered what that bag was for.
Yes.
Well, as I'm sure you know,
it's inferior to your baking.
Your stomach may spite you.
Don't diss your own gift.
Oh.
Chocolate ganache squares?
I love ganache.
I'm such a dummy.
Making gifts with care is one thing,
but wrapping them with care completes the gesture.
I was too focused on taste to fret about presentation.
Oh, this plate's from your house.
Kind of comforts me.
Huh?
He's really chowing down.
Are they good?
They're very good.
Just sweet enough.
Here, try one before I inhale them.
Say, ah.
It's tasty, right?
I guess so.
Beats the practice batch.
By a long shot.
Hard to relax till you see how your partner reacts.
Huh?
Hmm?
He felt the same way I did.
How's the cake?
Do you approve?
What?
Everything you make is delicious.
Of course I approve.
You had another relief.
How am I supposed to eat with you staring at me?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Chocolate cake that simply melts in your mouth.
Whipped cream that isn't too sweet.
Just how I like it.
Now what should I make next here?
Stop!
Too soon!
You're gonna eat it, right?
Do you even have to ask?
It's something that only I'll get to taste.
Have you thought about what you're gonna make for me?
This is gonna be hard to top.
I like his word and cute as you did today and it'll be a win.
AVERT YOUR EYES!
I can't look at your face!
He put his whole heart into that cake and it tasted like happiness.
I like it.
The cake and the cake and have mindfulness.
Thank you.
Oh, hi, Sawada.
All the seniors are leaving soon.
I know.
I can't do it.
Should have known since I can't even talk to the boys in class.
What an awful excuse that is, right?
I'm sorry.
You were such a huge help, but it was all for nothing.
Hey, I can go give it to him.
That's not the issue here.
She wanted to give it to him herself.
What a waste of perfectly good chocolate.
But at least a shopping trip is a nice memory.
Thank you.
Wait.
Then let me have the chocolate.
But you said I could have it if you didn't give it to him.
That way it won't go to waste.
I'll eat all of it.
Really?
Even if you hate the flavor?
Okay.
It's yours.
Thanks.
Here.
Trade ya.
I got it yesterday.
For you.
What do they call these gifts?
Obligatory?
Or whatever?
I really appreciate this.
It isn't some obligatory chocolate, though.
It's friendship chocolate.
I'm sorry.